const chemistrySeed = [
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the term for everything in the universe that occupies space (you, the computer in front of you, your drink, and the air your breathing?',
    correctAnswer: 'Matter',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Who cares?',
        2: 'Vaccuum',
        3: 'The Upside Down'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the smallest division of an element that still has the same properties?',
    correctAnswer: 'Atom',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Proton',
        2: 'Neuron',
        3: 'Molecule'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the positively charged subatomic particle?',
    correctAnswer: 'Proton',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Magnents'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the negatively charged subatomic particle?',
    correctAnswer: 'Electron',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Proton',
        2: 'Neutron',
        3: 'Magnentism'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the neutrally charged subatomic particle?',
    correctAnswer: 'Neutron',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Proton',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Magnentism'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'Which subatomic particle has a negligable mass compared to the others?',
    correctAnswer: 'Neutron',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Proton',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Isotope'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is mass number of any Isotope?',
    correctAnswer: 'Neutrons plus Protons',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Protons plus Electrons',
        2: 'Electrons plus neutrons',
        3: '69 amus'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the Cosmic Speed Limit as far as we now know?',
    correctAnswer: 'The Speed of Light',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'The Speed of Sound',
        2: '5 mph above whats posted',
        3: '8 million mph'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the name for 2 atoms of the same element that have a different number of Neutrons and therefore a different mass?',
    correctAnswer: 'Isotopes',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ions',
        2: 'Conjoined Twins',
        3: 'Cations'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'An atom gives away some electrons to achcieve a full valence shell. What would we now call it?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cation',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Anion',
        2: 'Electron Defficent Isotope',
        3: 'Sad'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'An atom recieves some electrons to achcieve a full valence shell. What would we now call it?',
    correctAnswer: 'Anion',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Cation',
        2: 'Electron Defficent Isotope',
        3: 'Sad'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'Where can you find the subatomic particles Neutrons and Protons?',
    correctAnswer: 'Nucleus',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Google',
        2: 'Craigs list',
        3: 'Electron Clouds'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'Where can you find the subatomic particles Electrons?',
    correctAnswer: 'Electron cloud orbiting the nucleus',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Google',
        2: 'Craigs list',
        3: 'Nucleus'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'Which subatomic particle defines an atom as a particular element?',
    correctAnswer: 'Proton',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Websters'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the zero point on the Kelvin temperature scale, equivalent to -273.15 degrees Celcius?',
    correctAnswer: 'Absolute Zero',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Freezing',
        2: 'Fahrenheit 451',
        3: 'Pretty Cold'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a compound that produces hydrogen ions in solution?',
    correctAnswer: 'Acid',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Base',
        2: 'Solvent',
        3: 'Ammonia'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the name for a positively charged particle emitted from a radioactive nucleus (identical to the nucleus of a helium atom?',
    correctAnswer: 'Aplha Particle',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Positron'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the number of representative particles contained in on mole of a substance?',
    correctAnswer: 'Avagadros Number',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: '8 billion',
        2: 'Avocados Slumber',
        3: 'Too many to count'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is emitted from some radioactive elements that is an electron resulting from the breaking apart of neutrons?',
    correctAnswer: 'Beta Particle',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Alpha Particle'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the quantity of heat needed to raise the temperature of 1g of pure water by 1 degree Celcius?',
    correctAnswer: 'Calorie',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Newton',
        2: 'Gravitron',
        3: '8 units'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a compound that produces hydroxide ions in solution?',
    correctAnswer: 'Base',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Acid'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the ratio of the mass of an object to its volume?',
    correctAnswer: 'Density',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: '5 to 9',
        2: '9 to 5',
        3: 'Enthalpy'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the term for energy waves that travel at the speed of light, including radio waves, infrared waves, visible light, ultraviolet waves, etc.?',
    correctAnswer: 'Electromagnetic Radiation',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Daltons',
        2: 'Sound Waves',
        3: 'Gamma Rays'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a protein that acts as a biological catalyst?',
    correctAnswer: 'Enzyme',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ester',
        2: 'Ether',
        3: 'Enantiomer'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the measure of the disorder of a system?',
    correctAnswer: 'Entropy',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Enthalpy',
        2: 'Messier',
        3: 'Chaos'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What process produces ethanol from sugars by the action of yeast or bacteria?',
    correctAnswer: 'Fermentation',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Photosynthesis',
        2: 'Cellular Respiration',
        3: 'Acidification'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the time required for one-half of the nuclei of a radioisotope sample to decay?',
    correctAnswer: 'Half-life',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Half-cell',
        2: 'Half-reaction',
        3: '8 years'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the name for an element in Group 8A of the periodic table, with a full valance shell?',
    correctAnswer: 'Noble Gas',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Metalloid',
        2: 'Metal',
        3: 'Satisfied'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the unit of frequency, equal to one cylce per second?',
    correctAnswer: 'hertz',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Electromagnetic Radiation',
        2: 'Daltons',
        3: 'Newtons'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What kind of molecule has one side slightly negative and the other side slightly positive?',
    correctAnswer: 'Polar',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ionic',
        2: 'Electric',
        3: 'Acidic'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What kind of bond has atoms that are shared unequally?',
    correctAnswer: 'Polar Covalent',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Ionic',
        2: 'Isotopic',
        3: 'Brotherhood'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a quantum of light, a discrete bundle of electromagnetic energy that interacts with matter similarly to particles?',
    correctAnswer: 'Photon',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Positron'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the process by which nuclei emit particles and rays?',
    correctAnswer: 'Radioactivity',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Emulsion',
        2: 'Evolution',
        3: 'Entropy'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is an isotope that has an unstable nuclei and undergoes radioactive decay?',
    correctAnswer: 'Radioisotope',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Positron',
        2: 'Hydrogen',
        3: 'Cation'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a very large molecule formed by the covalent bonding of repeating monomers?',
    correctAnswer: 'Polymer',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Isomer',
        2: 'Merkel Disc',
        3: 'Polar Molecule'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is a quantum mechanical property fo electrons that may be thought of as clockwise or counterclockwise?',
    correctAnswer: 'Spin',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Time',
        2: 'Quarks',
        3: 'pH'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What are molecules that have atoms in the same order, but which differ in the arrangement of the atoms in space?',
    correctAnswer: 'Stereoisomers',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Isotopes',
        2: 'Anions',
        3: 'Quarks'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the process in which a solid changes to a gas or vapor without passing through the liquid state?',
    correctAnswer: 'Sublimation',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Sublime',
        2: 'Evaporation',
        3: 'Condensation'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is any substance that interferes with the hydrogen bonding between water molecules and thereby reduces surface tension(i.e. soap)?',
    correctAnswer: 'Surfactant',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Solute',
        2: 'Solvent',
        3: 'Titrate'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the measure of the average kinetic energy of particles in matter, which determines the direction?',
    correctAnswer: 'Proton',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Neutron',
        2: 'Electron',
        3: 'Websters'
      }]
  },
  {
    category: "63960b9ccd6b86a544c3a50b",
    question: 'What is the word for everything that is, ever has been, or ever will be?',
    correctAnswer: 'Cosmos',
    incorrectAnswers: [
      {
        1: 'Me',
        2: 'My life',
        3: 'My social media'
      }]
  },
]

module.exports = chemistrySeed